(This story is entirely fictional)
(The computer shows a copy history.
What is she afraid of?)
(Who's she trying to protect? Jin Keke.)
(Wen saw it.
She couldn't pretend not to.)
(What she brought back; A USB drive
was tampered. The files were copied.)
(Based on the novel
Doctor Qin: Executer)
(No!)
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 25=
(In Loving Memory
of My Daughter, Xia Wen)
Stop crying!
What good is crying?
Will crying bring Xia Wen back?
I'm sorry...
What exactly happened that night?
(Of course,)
(Back then, she didn't have the courage
to confess)
(what happened that night.)
(Whatever,)
(Le Tianyi and Zhang Xiaodong
started it all.)
(I'll make them die miserably.)
Keke,
I cry holding the photo album every day.
You think I'm losing my mind?
No.
Every day, I live in misery, wide awake.
Every day I remind myself
not to forget.
(Photos and notes)
Xia Wen didn't know
how wicked people can be,
so she died.
But you crawled out of darkness.
You've tasted betrayal and despair.
So you understand darkness better.
Are you still
the Jin Keke in the abyss,
manipulated by bad buys?
Remember.
That crying, weak Jin Keke
already died with Xia Wen!
The person you've become
is someone carrying Xia Wen's resentment
and all of Jin Keke's pain,
the Executer.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Keke, what is this place?
A place where no one disturbs us
to settle old scores.
(She rented this place with money)
(extorted from the bosses.)
(Her drive exceeded my expectations.)
(Maybe she's been like me
all these years,)
(thinking about how to take revenge
every moment.)
Keke.
I probably won't hold on much longer.
Mom, what nonsense?
The doctor said
(Discharge diagnosis)
maybe in a year or two,
(Alzheimer's)
I might not remember anything.
I won't remember Wen's face,
or how she died.
I won't even remember the names
of our enemies.
I'm afraid after I go down there,
Wen will ask me.
Mom,
did you avenge me?
But I don't even remember those enemies.
Keke.
While I still remember,
let's do it now, okay?
I don't want to leave with regrets.
Keke.
Promise me, okay?
Okay.
I promise you.
If you don't let me out,
I won't take a single sip!
Let me go!
(I know, but what can I do?)
(I hate her,
but I can't live without her.)
You wretch!
Let me out!
The person in the cage
is also the one who built it.
She imprisoned souls,
only to be consumed by hunger.
Listen,
the cats out there are hungry.
They're licking an impure heart.
This is the first judgment
and also a declaration.
Retribution has come.
Every sin will be paid for.
Mom.
They believed what I said.
Don't call me Mom!
I never treated you as my daughter.
Mom...
What's wrong?
I haven't done enough?
Mom...
Mom, what else do I have to do?
Tell me.
I'm not your mom!
And you were never my daughter!
Mom...
Are you abandoning me?
Who'd truly love someone
who killed her own daughter?
Mom!
She choked me!
I didn't mean to...
After Jin Keke met with the lawyer,
she was like a soulless shell.
Look.
(Interrogation Room)
When is my mom coming to see me?
Ms. Song wanted me to tell you
she doesn't want to see you ever again.
She never treated you as her daughter.
Why?
Tell me!
Tell her to come see me.
Tell her to come see me!
Don't touch me!
Jin Keke, watch your attitude!
Keke.
Haven't you ever felt
she's using you?
Some things
are too painful to know.
Just let me live in the story I chose.
"Jin Keke is very smart and obedient.
So in the police's eyes,
there's only Jin Keke
without time to commit the crimes.
The real killer was always me."
(And I'm just an old woman)
(with Alzheimer's
who lost her only child.)
(This plan isn't flawless,)
(but at least it can stall)
(until we can finish everything.)
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Keke.
What exactly did Le Tianyi do to Wen?
Wen, she...
Never mind.
Grandma Song!
Niu,
I'll take you to a nice place.
Okay?
We didn't expect...
We didn't expect
Le Tianyi'd be cowardly enough
to turn himself in.
The plan was thrown into disarray.
Luckily Wang Xuan was following him.
You said last time
you had Wang Xuan get off halfway.
It wasn't my idea.
Ms. Song changed her mind.
She decided
to execute Le Tianyi herself.
Most importantly,
she didn't want
to ruin Wang Xuan's life.
Wang's already...
Wang's suffered so much.
Get off. Take Wang Xuan away.
Hurry up.
Why?
You still have Niu to raise.
(Fan A 65800)
Who is it?
Who are you?
I'm Xia Wen's mother.
What Xia Wen?
I don't know her!
Do you know who I am?
Listen to me. It was an accident.
I didn't kill her.
It wasn't me.
I didn't kill her!
Let me go!
I have kids too.
I also...
You dare mention Niu?
How did you treat Wang Xuan and Niu?
It wasn't me...
Pigs eat anything.
Dirty, rotten, abandoned things.
They never pick.
Today the pigs will eat you!
That's what your sins deserve!
Wake up, Le Tianyi...
Wake up...
The Executer is never absent.
What is all this?
Help!
- Hypocrites nest atop the tower.
- Help!
- Grinding her struggles into stairs.
- Save me!
Boiling her tears into soup.
This man
is like a pig that's never full.
Turning Le Tianyi into pig feed
wasn't something
Ms. Song could do alone.
You and Wang Xuan both have alibis.
Who's the other accomplice?
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪